Hello everyone, good evening, today I am the anchor Tina, then today we will carry out a
design and production course on the spring and summer atmosphere. The final effect of this course today
is probably what we have just seen, which is to make such a dress group
first, I will lead our demographic models
to harmonize this surface to pit high
the next words, about the one production design process of this dress group
as an designed for like
this year we will begin a series of this kind of long shortly live lectures on how the designer
took care of in
design and production of clothing in the cloud software.
As a designer,
it may not necessarily have a complete paper sample in hand at the beginning.
Under such a background,
how should the designer
successfully design and produce a style in the cloud software?
Today, I will demonstrate from the perspective of a paperless sample.
First of all, you can see this pattern just now.
We can see this white picture.
This pattern is a model that I want to present in the end.
I can take a look at it.
The upper body is basically a design that is similar to the top of a neckline dress.
The lower body is mainly an A-shaped dress.
Considering that I don't have a paper sample in my hand,
this kind of upper body neckline dress
is a model that is similar to the top of a neckline dress.
We can start directly from the 3D pen tool of the cloud software.
I can draw a model on the model.
I can use any type of top of a neckline dress
that I want to use the 3D pen tool of the cloud software to complete it very well.
I just drew a little crooked here.
Let's find the center and start.
Find the front and draw a line.
Then, when you see the picture I just drew,
you can see that the shape of the line is a little like a half-moon cup.
So I will make the first point of my cup shape
is a relatively low chest.
Then come to this side.
We can extend it directly to the position of its side.
Then I will draw the curve of the curve point here.
I pressed the control key.
Come to the side.
I will loosen it up.
Press the control key to draw a straight line.
At this time, I can press the shift key to help find a straight line.
But I don't want it to be too straight.
A little bit forward.
Maybe this shape will look more comfortable.
Then this line should not be too high.
OK.
Then,
there is one in the front.
I want to make a high and low gap from the side to the front of this upper body.
So next, I will use the shape of the curve to complete this line.
OK.
If the shape is finished,
we can use this editor 3D pen tool to adjust it very conveniently.
For example, I want to pull this point down a little bit.
Make the front look smoother.
OK.
Then this side is also.
Come to the side and look at this gap.
See if it fits.
For example, this position.
I hope it goes back a little bit.
Just move it directly.
OK.
For example, in this position.
I think this place is too old.
We can also right-click here to add a point or add a curve point.
For this side, I want to adjust its curve.
So you can add a curve point.
Adjust this side a little bit.
OK.
In this way, my first half is almost done.
Next, I will adjust this point a little bit.
A little bit forward.
It was not adjusted just now.
OK.
Next, I will draw the second half.
This is the back piece.
I will also draw it.
Give it a little curve.
Then find the position of the back of my body curve.
At this time, you can press the Shift key.
Let it be vertical.
Draw it.
Then draw it again.
Here, I press the Shift key.
Its height is wrong.
It doesn't matter.
We can just press it here.
Just click here.
OK.
At this time, I can adjust it a little bit.
Let it go up a little bit.
OK.
In the middle of the back, it looks like this.
It's almost done.
It's a little bit lower than this place.
Make it a little bigger.
OK.
It's almost done like this.
Then this style.
This style.
Just this style.
I have a pattern in the place of the princess line.
That includes the back of it as well.
I want to make a shape of a smite.
So there is also a pattern.
Now I will draw a pattern line for it.
OK, I can come to the front and look at it.
Around this position,
At this time I can press the Shift key.
OK.
It's about the same.
It's almost this line.
Of course, if you think the composition is not very good,
you can adjust it again.
OK, then we come to the middle.
It's the same.
The back is on the side,
about two-thirds of the position.
Add a line to it.
Of course, if you think this position is not very good,
you can also adjust it.
In the process of adjustment,
the line may become a straight line.
Now this looks more smooth.
If it doesn't look smooth,
you can consider adding a curve point and adjust it again.
In this way,
my half-side shape is completed.
Next, I will use the flat flat plate tool
to select the single machine.
Just press it.
Then press it again.
Press the return key.
There is a hint at the bottom of our mouse.
Let's take these paper samples out.
When it is taken out,
it may be a little messy.
Let's sort it out a little bit.
You can rotate it like this board.
In addition to this rotation,
we can use the right key to rotate the Y-axis.
Then select the back middle line as the basis
to perform a Y-axis alignment.
Then the side can also be slightly rotated a little bit.
In this way,
let's take a look at its private line direction.
Basically, they are all relatively Y-axis.
So at this time,
we can directly select the right key on any board.
Use this to align it with the direction of the golden sand according to the Y-axis arrangement.
Then that's it.
Then we align the other side for it.
Press D.
In this case,
we can also align it directly to the back middle.
Then we use the edit board function in the back middle.
After we do that,
we can put it together,
then it's just a horizontal symmetry.
After we put it together,
it's just a horizontal symmetry.
In that case,
it looks a little bit uneven here.
I hope it is in a more straight shape.
We can delete all the lines on the right.
Then we put it a little bit lower.
Or we can lift this point up.
Or like this.
Arrange, go up, this doesn't work
Lift it up a little bit to make it straight
The back is also to delete all curve points to make it straight
Of course, you can also do this, directly remove the joint
After removing the joint, we directly align this point
And here is the same
Arrange, and align the bottom
This way, it can be assured that it can be aligned
It is a straight state
Then in the front, we sew it here
After sewing, the shape here is exaggerated
What we actually do is
This breast is a state where there is no curve
So we can consider moving this position forward
In order not to change the curve shape when moving
I can press the first key on the keyboard
To make a adjustment
Let it not be so sharp
Then here is also
You can correct it a little bit
Then simulate
It will fall down when you simulate, right?
It doesn't matter, let's cancel it
In order to prevent it from falling down
We actually talked about it in the previous class
I can use the model measurement to fix it
But because it is a curve here
Not very convenient
Then we can freeze it directly
I add a shoulder strap to it
Fix it with a shoulder strap
The length of this shoulder strap is about 360
Of course, you can also draw a general length
Then adjust according to the wear effect
I will quickly sew it here
Look at the left and right symmetry
Set a left and right symmetry for it
Because in this way
When I sew it
Will be more
Wait a moment
Can be directly left and right symmetry
I will arrange this shoulder strap
I sewed the wrong direction
Please sew it
It is on this side
You can see if its position is suitable
If it looks like its position is not very suitable
You can also adjust it to it
Or just move to the side here
Move this a little bit to the middle
Prevent it from sliding down later
Then copy the other side of the symmetry
At this time, you can see that it is sewn directly
Simulate
At this time, it will slide down, right?
It doesn't matter
Let's reduce the diameter a little bit
Because this board is very narrow
Simulate again
It's not as good as it was just now
Come back a little
In order to prevent the shoulder strap
In the process of simulation
Fall down
We can fix this armor to the model
This tool on the body
Give it a position near the inner edge
Fix it first
Pull it out a little bit
A little bit closer to the inside
Come out a little bit more
OK, let's fix this position for him
Just press it
Here, I
Fix this place for him first
Go in a little bit
Here, I can also
The position is not suitable
You can find this point of red inside
Let him go a little bit inside
OK
Almost
If the back can be pulled out a little bit
Adjust its position
Look at the position of these two panels
You can come in a little bit more here
OK
The model is adjusted to the skin state
It's easier to find this point
The white was a little too bright just now
OK
After I add this shoulder strap
I can
To simulate my front half
OK
After that
We are now
The shape of the upper body
Draw it out for him
OK
Then next
Let's take a look
I want to do his lower body
But before I do the lower body
I first put this one in the back
Do it for him
Then the shoulder strap
We can fix it first
OK
Then the smoker
Come to this panel
This panel
We can do it first
a
Ah
Create this
The inner line
Ah
It's a little crooked
So we can do this here
Unlock it first
And then
Give it up and down
After selecting the weight together
Click on the inner line between the lines
Then we will add a little more
Add to
You look at it
This square
Width is almost
Good
How much do I add now
Take a look
It's about ten
OK
Then make it
Directly make a column layer
Outside
Make a column layer for him
Wait a minute
Good
Then after the column layer comes out
I will come next
Just put the outer layer of this panel
Just put it wide
In order to prevent the connection inside
So let's get rid of the connection first
Then give him
Find the center of this
The origin
Use the adjustment panel tool
Double click
After that
See these dots
It's done
At this time
You can use this center
As a basis
Go
To this panel
Go out
Ah
Left click
Hold down the left key
Drag
Without loosening
Right click at the same time
That this
I'll probably put it
This is a little too much
About
Put 1.5 to 2 times
Can make it
Obvious
Tracking effect
Good
After coming out
Next can also be simulated
In order to prevent
Influence the front part
We can freeze it first
Good
Now simulate
It will definitely not be stable
Because of this panel
The particle range is too large
We can take it
First
Moderate
10 or 8
All right
Try not to give it
Reduce it to too small
Then at this time
Why do I keep it?
In order to make it
Can be better
To fix it
One
Ah
Smart
A form
Then here
We can add one
Flour
Use our
Ah
Sticky attribute
Put it on our
On the inside panel
Then
Give it to him
Add flexible
Fold
Or
We can directly select the inner line
Add one
Flexible
100%
A setting
Just these two
The logic is all right
Yes
I fixed the length of the inner layer
Set 100% flexibility
Let him just keep it
2D size
Or you
According to
Ah you put
Just put out
The size of this panel
Go
Ah
With
This
The original length
Minus your current length
Get a
Percentage
You can set it
Flexibility is also possible
Ah
Here
In this way
To deal with
OK
It's a little bit of a problem now
It doesn't matter
We are now
Just put this
The panel
Give it appropriate
Reduce it
Here
Can be reduced
Reduce
And the side seam is also re-seam, just seam it like this, OK, and this side is also because I just unseamed the joint.
Then, for all the sewing lines that have just been sewn, all of them have to change its sewing line type to fold seam, in order to make it more even.
In this case, our effect is OK.
Now, it may be that the fold is not very delicate and real, because now the particle diameter is not enough.
We will reduce it at the end in order to avoid affecting our overall simulation speed.
Now here, I will use the shortcut Ctrl J to activate this part for it.
In this case, it will not take up too much computing power later.
Next, let's make it a skirt.
You can consider moving these two panels first.
And then make a skirt.
For the skirt, because I want to make a skirt that has a certain degree of transparency,
so we need to make a lining in it to prevent it from fading.
Let's make a lining first.
For the lining, I will do it in the simplest way.
First, measure the length of my front panel.
Use the editor to select the line section, and you can measure it.
My 2D length is about 176.6.
I can insert it around, it is about 180.
Then we use the ruler.
Use this curved panel to adjust it to 180.
The height is about 400.
Of course, this can also be adjusted later.
Then I will make it symmetrical.
First, I will make the lining.
I will give it to it first.
Use this extension panel line tool.
First, make a lining of its A shape.
The inner part of the line section is 180.
Then I can slightly shrink it a little bit,
so that the lining is also a little bit.
It's a state of drawing.
You can just add a little bit to it.
Then the line section 2.
Of course, it's best not to draw too much of the lining.
Otherwise, it will make it look very ancient outside.
In fact, the front panel is actually because we don't have that smart.
Even if it's a long-term problem, it's not big.
What about the line section 2?
You have to open it up.
Here, if you multiply it by 2,
it's about 360.
Probably open it up to these amounts.
Or actually, the lining doesn't have to be opened up a lot.
We can make it a little bit smaller.
It can come according to the effect you see.
300.
Then we can predict the shape of it.
Then I let it go in one direction.
Confirm.
Then I can make it symmetrical in the front.
In this way, a lining in front of me will come out.
Then next, let's look at the back.
In the back, there is one plus this.
Because I canceled the left and right symmetry of the back.
Of course, you can put it in the left and right symmetry.
It can't be set now.
Select it together.
After selecting, see the one in the back.
Do half is fine.
The length of the back half is 133.
45, 133.
Here you need to pay attention.
I should have chosen this.
I shouldn't have chosen short.
Why?
In fact, when the human body is wearing it,
it is stretchable here.
So in the back,
my inner skirt must follow it.
The amount is enough to pull.
So we can consider to put these two on.
It's about 193.
Then I turn it around.
It's about 200.
The height is 400.
It's the same length as just now.
Confirm.
Then we put this in the same way.
Give it.
Open the amount of A version.
It's about 200.
The length is about 200.
How much to open?
According to the effect,
this is too much.
200, 300.
Then it's this.
A little more.
If this amount is not appropriate later,
you can adjust it again.
Give it a symmetrical spread.
Here.
I'm going to add a little bit more to the back of the pleats
And sew it like this
Okay, I can use the level to flip it over and drag it over and simulate it.
Of course, you can also use the arrangement point.
The amount on the back side will be a little more.
Then we put this group.
Obviously, this length is not long enough.
It doesn't matter. We can drag it directly.
When dragging, it will affect my rhythm.
It doesn't matter. I'll just take a look.
If the amount is not enough, you can put it again.
In order to see the obvious effect, I will make this a little smaller.
Here, the problem occurs because of the curve in front of me.
The curve is too high.
At this time, we can do this.
Put it down a little bit in the front.
OK.
Then in the back, because I just did the draw,
so there is a little curve in the back.
There is no big problem here.
Wait a minute and adjust it for him.
Then in the front, I hope to do this.
Give him this amount again.
Let's do a release link first.
Let him open this amount for him a little bit.
All of them.
OK.
Then what about the back of us?
Use a softer fabric for him.
Here, let's just put this one first.
OK.
Add a fabric.
Let's first.
You can give him this a little bit.
Give him a little bit of his amount.
A little bit.
The amount above is a little bit smaller for him.
OK.
It is so much that it is not so exaggerated.
Let him not be so exaggerated.
Then what about the inside?
This state of it?
Put it here first.
Later I'm going to make the material outside.
I will also put it in.
That here, we are going to use the fabric we just used.
This fabric we just used this this this.
The fabric of mingled is very hard.
Is the material we put inside to support it.
So, give him a little bit of better.
A little.
So use the correct sound material to make it look more normal.
OK, then we will do the outer layer.
For the outer layer, I will do it normally.
Let's take a look.
The outer layer here is divided into four pieces.
There are two pieces in the front and two pieces in the back.
Next, let's do it.
The idea he came up with is similar to our inner layer.
Here, I will probably...
Wait a minute, let me take a look.
We just looked at the wrong version.
Look at this.
For this,
because I see that there is a seam here,
so for the skirt,
there are two pieces in the front and two pieces on the front.
If you match it, there are four pieces in the front.
So let's do it according to this structure.
First of all, I will make a skirt with this length.
Then, make a skirt with the length of the side here.
And then finally, it's a skirt in the back.
It's probably a logic like this.
For the front, let's measure it.
It's probably 84.7cm.
It's probably 85cm.
We still use this type of fabric.
85cm.
Let's give it a little bit of volume.
Let it have a little bit of fold.
And then for the length,
we can give it to...
The length of the skirt is relatively long.
It can be up to 800cm.
And then, let's use this...
Use this...
It's also...
This is the open tool.
Let it go.
If it's open, I'll multiply the front by 2.
Confirm.
OK.
I didn't give a lot of the front side.
But if you think this is not enough,
Let's do it again.
It's okay to go to 300, just give it a little more
And then here you can see that there are two pieces in the front
And then we come to the side side, I want to give him a little more of the draw so that he can
We can take a look at the side of his draw is relatively large
Give him a little more in the front
OK, and then we also measure the length of the side first. It's about 150
But I hope that the side has a more dense draw so that he can
It's very thin on the waist and it's very thin on the waist so what about this side
It's about 150 and I'm going to give him a little more
Give him about 250
The height was 800 just now
And then we're going to take this amount
Give him
Make a
Let go
Actually, it's okay to set it according to the size I set here. It's okay to let go when you're drawing a board. Or you can let go of it here.
What about the side here?
I put it a little bigger
Multiply by 2 is 500
How much is 500 multiplied by 30? 750
Multiply by
Between 500 and 750, give him about 600
I can give him
All let the two sides to expand
Give it 3 times
Give him a little bigger
This is the other side, then I have the front side, and then I'll do my back
What about the back side?
It's also based on this number to do
Now it's 136
136 times 2
Then I'll do this first
Just do it according to his normal
Then use this
When opening the tool
136 times 2 is about 200
About
270 here
In the back, it was 136 just now, I can give him a little more, so that he has a little bit of a margin.
How much did we just give here?
Let's take a look
Probably more than the original
More than 60
Let's give him a look
Give him two
136 to 200
A little more, then this side is up to 400
Confirm
This is all based on the effect, let's see if we wear it on our body, if we feel that this amount of A is not very satisfied, we can adjust it again.
Then give him a symmetrical spread here
OK, then put this on the front of this group
This is to him
Then here is to this two side of the pinyin
Front middle
Side gap
Front middle side gap
Then it's the back middle
If the back middle, we will directly give him a whole because we just have this
The front of the back piece is left and right symmetrical
Directly
it is good
Give him a arrangement
Then the arrangement here is not very convenient to see here
After it is wrapped up, its position will change a little bit
It doesn't matter, we are waiting for this
In the element editor
Can open
Find this arrangement
Then in this arrangement here we can adjust it a little bit
First let him open a little bit
Of course, you can adjust it to the flat side, you can adjust it to the flat side, it is flat and it is also possible to put it in the state
The surface
Sometimes when we arrange a particularly large version, we can change it to that
Flat
Then we come to the side
This side is very exaggerated
This is none of our business
Come to this
Re-select it
Adjust its Y position
Then pull out
What about here
You can use
Flat
Give him a little more
So he won't fight with him
Then arrange the side
Back
The back is also
Put it in the wrong place
Put it on this point
Because we just saw his
The limit position of the Y-axis has not yet met our requirements
Hold it out a little bit
There is a little bit of this here
The gap is also not a big problem
If you especially
Just go inside
Then use this
You can pull it out with the positioning ball
Now the positioning ball I use is this
World coordinates
This is based on personal habits
Just set it
Then we can simulate it now
Before that, I froze it inside in order to avoid my skirt to affect my
The shape of the other parts can be used this hard
Support
Solve the hard words and then simulate
What about now
Note that the attribute is wrong
Use this default material attribute
OK
Okay, our group is already sitting on it
But now I can't see the details of this group
Did I use the full selection just now?
Full selection
Put this for him
Put it on my tablet
Then
Now I put my skirt
Slightly lower the particle diameter for him
Because I can't see the fold of this place
So let's lower it a little bit
I feel that the fold on this side
It doesn't seem very obvious
Let's lower it a little bit and take a look
The front and back are absolutely enough, but the side seems not very enough
Sure enough
It doesn't matter, I'll give it back
Just
Give him a simulation
What happened just now
Now this amount is not enough, what should I do?
It doesn't matter, let's put this
A little bigger
For my quick simulation
Didn't we just say that if you think this amount is not enough
Can you adjust it again
Let's adjust it again
Put this
The amount below
Make it bigger
All
Then the amount above is also not enough
How much was it just now
Put a little more on the top
Because we don't have enough fold on the top
Can be a little more
Let him fold a little more
Confirm
Just simulate it
You can also use hard drawing to help you to reorganize your form
Rearrange
After organizing, the simulation is ready
End hard drawing
Next, I can put mine
In addition to the shoulder belt, there is also my back
Other versions, let me simulate it together
You can see the front and middle
It's pulled very hard
What should I do at this time
Because my front and middle actually want to make
The same as the chest
State
At this time we can consider
Put my front and middle to him
Add a
Slipper
Or
Use a harder mouse
I choose the slipper here
In order to prevent it from being
Pulled down
OK
Then below this
It's widened for my chin
Can you see
We put the chin choice
Do that plus a elasticity
How much is the elasticity
100%
Prevent it from being stretched
So that it is more tight
Then my side
In fact, the front is slightly pulled down a little bit
At this time we can
in
This position
And my side bone position
Here
Make a stretch line in the position of the side bone
I can choose a relatively hard stretch line
Can't pull
You can take a look at this attribute or this attribute can also
It can't be pulled
Use this to
Stabilize this clothes
Prevent it from being
The gravity is pulled down
That actually includes my shoulder belt as well
The front of my shoulder belt is always default fabric
So it's easy to be pulled
At this time I can put my
Shoulder belt
Consider using this
The second piece of fabric we just chose
It is a hard-to-pull fabric, we can see that the strength of the gold tail gauze is very strong, it is not easy to be pulled
So you can choose this attribute
You can see that my clothes are pulled up
It's not easy
Appear this
A situation that can be turned down
Then I will still freeze it
OK good then I am now basically
I want to simulate
We just this shoulder
This position has been pulled to deform
That can be considered in this position also give it
Add a circle of this stretch line
To prevent it from deforming
It is also used for it to use this
A relatively hard stretch line
You can see that its shape has been restored
Let's freeze this for him
Then the skirt temporarily
For the time being, you don't have to adjust the skirt, so we can put the skirt first
It's also for him to freeze or anti-fire, I used anti-fire here
Next, I'm going to give him a detail in the front
That is, I have a detail of the pull in the front
Then here
The position in the front
You can see that there is a sewing line here
So we are here
Make an internal line
Make a
About 8mm
Give him
Make an internal line
Then give him a cologne layer
Outside
Outward cologne
Take it to the side
This layer is used for loud material
This layer I hope it is soft, I don't want to use a sticky layer, turn off its sticky layer
I choose it here
I find the cologne, turn off the cologne
Then we see this side
The cologne strip is not needed
Because the outer layer is a normal fabric
I hope it is soft
Then we put this
Right-click to unlock the link, use the adjustment board
What to do after unlocking the link
This board I hope it
There is a draw, so you have to zoom in on it
Choose it
I double-clicked the center point to activate it
Then do it for him
Do a 100% reduction, for example, adjust to 150%
Enlarge it
Then I also freeze it here to prevent it from affecting my internal layer
What about this layer?
The particle diameter must be small
For convenience, I will simulate it later when I see it
See if this amount is enough
Of course, if you want to see more, you can reduce the particle diameter to see
Including
Between this
This board
The contrast thickness can also be adjusted, but not now, wait a minute, we still have to do the outer layer, put it first
OK, after that, give it to the other side and align it, simulate it
If you think this amount is not enough, you can give it more
Put a little bit
All can
In this case
His amount is more
You can give him this
Like this
And then
There is a little bit of light below
We can consider this
Which corner
Turn off this flexibility
Turn off the flexibility
Let's give him this place to pull him straight
Like
Come back
That's it
I will add that later
You can't see this detail
Of course if you say you
Can't stand it
His details
Let's put this
Why does he look like this
Still the same as the previous problem, his outer layer of the sewing line because we are Ke Long
So his sewing line is also
It's wrong, the position is wrong, let's re-sew it
Give him this side
Choose this four edges
Change to fold
Re-simulate
This is normal
So don't be the same as me
I forgot this point
And then next
The pull is OK, let's find our
These two panels
I will freeze it
And then the outer skirt
I'm going to start activating
What to do with the activation
Didn't we just see him have this
The edge of the river
Let's do the edge of the river
Before doing the edge of the river
These two panels
I will freeze it first
Avoid
To have some influence
Then do the edge of the river, we have to take a look at it first
I will do two edge of the river
I will do two edge of the river in this gap
So to make it easier for me
A stability of simulation
Let's adjust the group first
How to adjust
Put our
This is the line that the edge of the river needs to be sewn to the object
Take it out here
You see here it is hidden
Then what to do
The amount here may be a little big
It doesn't matter, we can choose to give it the amount in the front
Smaller
So don't let this fold get into it
We just saw the fold in the front a little bit
Smaller
In this way, I recorded it in the front
Take a look at my side gap
The gap on the front side is also outside
OK
Of course you can also use one like this
Pause and make a needle here so that you can see this gap
It will be easier to simulate later
Easy
Wait for us to put
After the edge of the river is made
Simulation again
It's not a big problem if it's stuck inside
Then let's take a look at the front
Let's do this one first
The edge of the river
The edge of the river we use is our
In the design version
The spiral version tool in the creation version
That
Before the creation
We first have to see how long my river edge is created
Right
So we can select the front and middle
Then come to
Our
Here
See how long this line is because I have to add the edge of the river to this line
The total length of this line is
Here
About 1034
In order to make it easier, we directly use hard drawing
Open this group
This is the most convenient
I'll freeze it later
So I can see all my gaps
Pull this over a little bit
Freeze
We are here to find our spiral version
In a place where the background is blank, click it
Then here we say that there are more parameters to be set here
First of all, this inside is
Our side of the river
The middle point of the side of the inside
To my core is the core of the spiral
The width of the middle point
In this case, we can set it according to our own
Actual demand
Can be set a little smaller or a little bigger
If you set it too small, you can see that the version will transform
See this position
So don't be too small
Then
We
This length will follow
The adjustment of your parameters
It will have some adjustments
So we set it at the end
Let's set the other position for it first
The width of the side of the side is the width of this side of my side
I hope it is 60
Wider
Then give it 50 here
That is to say, I can see this picture
It's a bit like a fox
A fox festival
The top is wider and the bottom is narrower
So
I give it a little wider above and a little narrower below
Then this arrow refers to my
The middle point on the inside
To me
The width between the middle points of this board outside
In fact, it affects my spiral
A number of gaps
Set it to 140
Take a look at this current setting
Then this just said
Right
Then we see this river side
It actually has a certain number of drawbacks
There is also a certain number of drawbacks on the river side
Especially above
So we give it some
Abundant amount
Give it 1034
Give it 1300
Let him have a certain amount of abundance
What about above? I feel a little bit here
A little bit bigger
I hope it turns tighter
I can adjust the top
Smaller
So you can see this
This spiral board is very long
OK
Click to confirm that the spiral board in front of us has been generated
Then we are here first
Give it this board
Simulate it
Of course, pay attention to my side of this board is using this
Change the name to avoid waiting
Just
Ignore it
It is actually a sticky attribute
It is to help us with the shape
This is our
Sound
I still use the sound fabric
When sewing here, we just gave a certain amount of abundance
Then I hope there is a butterfly-shaped shape on it, so I want to give it a certain amount of drawbacks on it
In order to make it convenient for me to locate it later, this line in front of us
You can make some adjustments
That is, we can use this m to n free sewing
What to do
I sewed, for example, I hope it will be here
Break it
Go down
Enter, return to the car, the first part is over
The second part is also
I want to find this
Straight to the bottom
1 to n is equal to 1 to 2
Return
In this case, he can naturally find this break
At this time, we just need to give this sewing line to him
Explain m to n, you can see that I am now this sewing line is broken
I probably need to find this amount
What's next, I'll take mine
Still using m to n
I sewed this to my
Right side
Sew to
Sew our outer layer
With the layer of the corresponding board
Go out
Enter
I will sew this separately later, first sew this part
Why sew this part like this, so that I can find my 1 to 1, that is this position
Then we can give this amount a little more, because this
Give him a little more
A little more, so that he has a certain draw
Then the rest of the amount, we will directly
Give it all to us
You can see that he has a draw number in it
Then we put this board over
Direct
Just simulate it
Just let him simulate it
You can print it
Pull it out, let him do it
Organize this
Just now I seemed to be
As expected
Let's change it
It's still very convenient in the shell, if you change it directly, then you can simulate it
Then adjust the particle diameter of this board
If you don't adjust it, we can't
To adjust its details
Then at this time it keeps falling to the side, is it not related? Remember to change the type of this sewing line to a fold
Is it
The object of my sewing is this board and
This half
Then there should be a fold between them
You see if it is now
The orientation is not right
It doesn't matter, let's pull it a little bit
Or a faster way is to set a negative pressure for it
Because the negative is on the back, it will move to the back
This can also quickly make it have an orientation
I am now in the state of hardening to adjust, because it will be relatively easier to adjust
Let it go inside a little bit
it is good
Just here
Give it a copy on the other side
Take a look at the sewing line, it is directly symmetrical, directly simulated
Let's see if it penetrates inside, pull it out
Simulate again
it is good
Give it
Solve hardening and simulate again
After solving hardening, pay attention to this side of this negative pressure to be eliminated
Is to return to
Pressure, pressure to return it to zero
Simulate
Solve the pressure to simulate
Okay, what about here? I suggest you can add it to it
Fake sewing needle
You can add it on your board
But in order to find your point of view
You can't point to the next layer like this
But we can go to the second bottom to find it
This layer
Set it up a little bit
This side is also
I can't see it now, right? It doesn't matter, you can press the shortcut key out 2 or out 1
Out 2 is a single layer, I found this point
You can set it to its highest point
Then out 4 is its transparent picture
How about this
You can click on this first, and then click on this one, it will form a pair
I just
So we have two pairs now
Simulate
This is equivalent to
Set it to its shape of a butterfly knot
But if you look at this position, if this position is not very suitable
You can also make a adjustment to it
For example, here I hope it
Go down a little bit
Let it go up a little
That's it
Then we freeze these two first
The details are not very good now, it doesn't matter, we can improve the quality simulation at the end
Then we do the same logic on the side
Give it to him
Make it out
What about here, we can directly and mine
This line
To my
This line down
Then take a look at the length of these two lines is 1047.9
1047 is probably 1050, let's go back and forth
Ok
That's the same, we were 80 just now
Then 1050
But here, if you don't want to have a fold, it's 1050
But I can give it a little bit of a fold here
Then this side is
Give it
100 if the length is
Don't be as wide as before
Because it's a little bit
A little bit
Because I want to emphasize the butterfly knot in front of us
So a little bit narrow, the same is 50 below, which is a structure that is narrow above and below
Then what about this building
You can see that this building is now
Too wide, we can give it
The front is 140, but you can make it a little smaller, and now this building is still
A little big, we can give it 140
Reduce a little to 120
Then this side is also
I just said to give it a little more, so that it has a certain draw volume
Confirm
I just said that the input is wrong
Why is it so narrow
Come again
Above is 80
This first input
Because this will affect my
This number
Then the above one just said 100
This is 50
Maybe I was wrong just now
Then this is 1200, I hope to give it a little more
This is OK
Then we put this
Give it to us
Side to side
Also hard
Too far too far
Put it closer, you can use this quick arrangement in the upper right corner
Find a position
Put it closer
Then model
Of course you can also use this very quickly
It's okay to add this to the side
But it has a certain randomness, we can try it
Add to the outside
OK
Because we are with this
Go to the side
So
Add to its outside
Folding
Pay attention to the folding line, let it fall to the side
Good
This side is also
Come
Model
OK
Then we will do this side
Then we will activate this bottom board
This bottom board will not
Stabilize
Now you can let it model normally
Normal simulation with my
OK
Then let's take a look
Now
One of the shapes on my big body is actually almost done
Then
Next I don't want to give it a
Well, the neck
Let's do this neck
If the big body
We can all give it to the big body
Reactive
Make my simulation most efficient
The neck is very simple
We first give it a neck of a chain
That's the cloth
Here we can open
Model size
You can use the size of the editor to see its neck, which is about 298, we give it a little more, about 300
About
If you want to make it comfortable, you can give it to 310
We use this giant board
Give it 300
The degree is 10
Confirm
Then we put this
This is hidden for him
This is not needed
Open the arrangement
Then pay attention to this, this board is very small, so the diameter is a little smaller
Then
Give it a
Back to the middle
You can come back a little bit
Now let's simulate it
Take a look at it
The gap in the middle is relatively large, so we can select the model
Its surface diameter has been adjusted to 0
Note if
Because of this model, I may have adjusted it when I saved it
If you are directly from
Connexion
Download this Mia
Input it
It is admitted that the surface diameter is 3, remember to reduce it to 0
Go to production
Especially
Our
The neck and the upper body
In the process of making the neck
Put this down first
After the neck chain is adjusted
Next we will do it for him
That flower
I want to have a base plate
This base plate, I will probably
Press the Shift key to draw a positive source
I am based on this
A size of the neck
Draw a
This neck
This board has to be a little smaller
Then this board
You can give it a seam
For example
I just sewed it up
Of course, you can use a fake sewing needle to fix it up
Sew it up
Add it to the outside
It is very soft now, right?
We use this
Stain
Let it harden
it is good
Then what to do next? We are going to sew this flower
Then our today's practice is to do a
A relatively simple flower
Take a look at that flower
Make a simple flower
Just sew it up in a circle
What about this flower? First of all, I want to find its
The object of sewing
We can make it a little simpler, I'll give it to him
Let's start from the bottom
Let him open his mouth
Down
It can be less conspicuous
I just hand-sewn some internal lines
Of course this one
If you have any other
Some other
Software
For example, AI or
It is possible to draw these curves in the PS
Let's make it a little more dense
If you draw it densely
When you deal with its
Levels later
Need to spend more energy
Spend more time
Then we live
Don't draw so densely
I probably draw such a spiral
Let's adjust this
Press the first key to control the curve
Come a little more
Then I look at it next
The length of this curve is 194
Know
Then we give it to him
Circle-shaped board
Still a circle-shaped board
In fact, many women will use this tool
Circle-shaped board
Next let's take a look
Because of this board
The board of the flower
The board of the flower will be relatively smaller
So we can put this
Let's set the size first
Smaller
About the width is not so wide
Then that
Give it a little smaller
Then the length
Also a little shorter
I gave 120, I just gave one
Because anyway we are doing flower
This must be
The state of the draw
So it must be longer than we just measured
I'm doing half now, and then we will do another half
It's like using two to fight it out
Now it is
Then this, we can't be too big
A little smaller
It's about this shape, it's slowly there, I think it can be shorter in the middle
A little deformed
It's almost like this
This is my one, and then I will do another one
It can be divided here
But we don't have to divide so much, I just took a look at this total length
194, then we probably divide to
It's just the right half, divide it in half
Because I will fight two sections up
It's almost divided to 98 or so
It's not very accurate
I can right-click, it's about 98
Confirm
Then we put the other section
With our
This one to do a balance
OK
This version is too big for him to adjust the gradient index
Divide it first
Reverse the version and divide the line
He will stay on one side for a while
Divide this version first
Note that when dividing, we have to freeze these two, or else the force when it is entangled will pull it into the shape
Reverse the pot
Do it with the reverse pot method first
The gradient index is a little smaller
OK
What about this flower
You can see that it looks like this now
It's soft
Take it out
He should be
Come out this way
Wait a minute, this
Let's go to 3
You may need to use the selection grid tool
Or add it to the side to take a look
No
Reset
Let's use this selection grid
Comparison tool
Help him
Now our center position
He should be in
More inside
Take it out
It is equal to the human support
Let him find the correct position
Then this half
Come out
Simulate
OK
Take this one out
Let's reset it
Use the hard material to simulate the shape
Pull it twice to find its position
It looks a bit angry
Give them two together
I haven't found their location yet.
Let's sort one out first.
This one is inside.
I need help to sort it out.
Let's see where they are now.
This one.
Let's sort it out.
Done.
OK.
Let's sort this one out.
Let's rearrange the location.
When doing this,
the key is to find the location of the spiral.
I'll try.
Let's put it in its place.
Since they join across from each other,
we should be able to sort it out.
Hold and hold it up.
它这里应该下来的,先反击火线,让它这个位置先找到,好了,位置找到了,一起模拟一下。
现在呢,它现在这个花朵的一个基础的一个轮廓是出来了的,但是我们还要就是做出它的一个花朵张开的一个这种自然生动的感觉了。
现在呢,我把这个版片再用回,我们把大绳布料,我们现在可以把那个我们等一下要用的这个大绳面料先加载进来,丝绸的一个面料,加进来。
这个面料。
这个面料怎么是有印花的,给它拿掉。
然后呢,我们把这个两个版片用这个大绳的面料。
我们用的是这个比较丝绸的面料,它是比较轻盈的。
然后呢,我们把这个给它做一个克隆层,克隆层是往它的内和外都可以。
为什么做克隆层?
因为它有这个花朵的这种,我们真实缝纫出来的这种。
把这个颜色的透明度先拿掉,看得清楚一点。
可以用这个来看一下。
是为了让它能够有这种厚度感。
OK。
我们把这个粒子进去调下来一下。
我们把这个粒子进去调下来一点。
后面有点不稳定,所以要拉出来一点。
刚刚不能这么拉。
一起往外拉。
要一起往外拉。
如果单层拉会穿层。
好。
那现在两层有了之后呢,我们可以把这个缝纫线,它现在是一个互相缝的状态。
我们可以先保留这样。
然后刚刚我们说它有一个像花朵一样张开的这种感觉。
我们可以给它缝一个非常非常长的一个板片。
可以量一下。
它的长度是800。
我们可以缝一个800,一半是400,那就是1200。
800加400,1200。
然后呢,这个宽度可以窄一点。
那这个条条给它缝在外面就可以给它带来那种。
缝到这儿。
然后缝到这儿。
OK。
缝到它的外边上。
然后我们给它添加到侧面。
看它添加的位置。
不太准确,添加到外面吧。
到它的外面。
那这个板片呢,粒子间去小一点,给到3。
那这个板片呢,因为它比较长,它自然而然会让这个花朵张开来。
那这里的话要给它,为了给它一个强支撑力,我们用这个粘衬的布料模拟。
你可以看到这样子花朵就张开来了。
我可以测一下,如果我们用的是丝绸面料的话。
你可以看到它就是张的很规律。
所以我们要给它用一个比较硬的布料,让它能够把这个里面的布料给它撑开。
那现在就有一个张开的这种花朵的感觉。
那这个布料呢,我现在给它回到这个白膜状态啊。
那这个布料呢,我们看到一个是边,对吧。
还有一个是我们的这个里层啊。
那我等一下,我们不希望看到这个板片,对不对。
我可以复制一个透明的。
把我的这条边,还有我的后片的这个里布,给它里面这层选中。
因为实际的衣服上不会有这些东西啊。
我给它应用一下,把它的这个透明度,不透明度调到0。
那这样的话,我们就可以看到它这个边边就看不到了。
那现在这个花花它就是一个比较立体的状态。
那现在我们这个花花呢,两层很平整,对不对。
我们可以这样啊,把这两个,把刚刚我们这个缝线,给它删除掉。
让它里外缝,里外。
然后包括这里。
是跟,这里是里外缝啊。
这里也是里外缝。
注意方向。
那这里的话是跟我们的这里是缝的。
因为我们刚刚这里也是,它是一个接缝的位置。
然后把我们刚刚缝线的,缝的这些线啊。
别选错了。
还有这个,这里面没有缝啊。
把我们刚刚缝的这些线呢。
这条线。
这条,这条。
这条。
不是这条,这条啊。
改成这个,是拼缝。
拼缝的关系,我让它有一个厚度感的话。
我们可以把这个折叠角度是180度。
让它呢,有一定的这个,加强它的强度。
等于让它这个边缘就是有一定弯弯的感觉。
就有给它增加了一些力。
因为我们这边是有花朵张开的感觉嘛。
所以它这个张开的这个效果呢。
可能不是那么的明显。
因为它这个地方有一个张开的力在啊。
那我们这个花朵呢,就差不多了。
我们现在一起解除,解除了这个冷冻。
我们可以看一下。
然后我现在把我的这个大绳的面料呢。
给它用在我们的这个大绳上。
接下来我们进入下一个环节。
跟大家说一下,就是关于花型的一个设置。
诶,没有用上啊。
把它拖上来。
放到这里来吧。
我们把这个删了。
我们可以选择这个。
在选中一个版片右键选择相同属性之物。
然后把它一起应用到我们的这个大绳的面料上来。
这个面料它是有一定的透明度的啊。
我是希望它有一定透明度。
然后呢,看一下我们这个面料的一个纹理。
啊,纹理的话呢。
我是希望用一个,诶,类似于是这个样子的一个。
呃,糟纱的这种感觉吧。
我的发现图,还有我的这个呃,表面粗糙度的一个贴图一起用上。
那现在它有一定的糟纱的效果。
那接下来呢,我要对它进行一个花型设计了。
那我可以来到我的这个。
嗯。
叫,我们打个,找到纹理啊。
找到我们的纹理编辑器,打开。
那首先呢,我的底纹是要保留的。
所以底纹这边呢,我会把它的,嗯,这个。
纹理给它冲淡颜色。
啊,然后接下来呢,我们就需要。
一般我们去设计花型的时候,会有一些花型的元素。
就是你想要设计什么样风格的。
那我这边找了一些花朵的一个元素。
那接下来就很简单。
我们就把这个花朵元素给它拖到我们的这个窗口里面来。
啊,然后呢,比如说这朵花。
哎,我让它小一点。
放在一个位置上。
然后呢,我们可以给它加一个。
比如说啊。
绿叶。
同样的也是小一点。
好。
那这个呢,我可以给它。
旋转一下。
啊,把我的这个花朵呢,给它挪过来。
那当然我可以调整它的图层。
让它看谁在上,谁在下。
这是一个花。
啊,比如说呢。
嗯,再比如说呢,我想给它加一个。
嗯,晕染的一个效果。
有点水墨,晕染的感觉。
啊,加一个。
那这个的话,我可以给它做一个。
嗯,就是透底纹的。
我可以给它做一个。
嗯,哪个来着。
可以试一下。
是哪个。
啊,颜色。
啊,给它拿过来。
啊,旋转一下。
啊,这个晕染呢,我可以做大一点。
那这个晕染,我可以让它做到一个。
啊,延伸。
让它能够跨缝。
啊。
大概在这里。
然后呢,我还可以给它再加一些,比如说。
啊,绿叶啊,花朵啊,等等的啊。
给它做,随便做一些效果。
比如说这边呢,我可以给它加一些独立的花瓣。
有点像花瓣飘落的感觉。
啊,再,再给它做一些小花瓣。
嗯。
那你在调的过程中呢,其实。
像这里的话,可以做一个类似于正片结底啊之类的。
都可以啊。
那我这边的话就用这个正常吧。
啊。
然后呢,再给它加一个大花花。
没加到啊,给它做一个夸缝,延伸,再用一个小的这个绿草,拖进来。
这个绿草你可以把它的层级放低一点。
也是延伸。
好,我就以这个为例,那你可以看到我现在就已经完成了这个应用并关闭就可以了。
那这样的话,通过一些元素呢,
通过一些图案的这种叠加,你可以快速的在Clue里面去完成一些简单的花形设计。
那在这里呢,如果你设计完成之后呢,我们在这可以找到你设计的这个花形的一个单循环,就可以把它拿出来用。
那我们这边的话呢,把这边隐藏掉,把这个线条隐藏掉,你可以看到它大概的一个效果。
打开这个3D的渲染,可以很清晰的看到。
那我这边再复制一个面料。
这个面料呢,我是用在里衬上的。
这个是不透明的。
然后这个面料呢,它应该是一个,在库里面找一个吧。
库里面找一个,针丝的一个,双周纱,在这儿啊。
把它应用在我们的礼布上。
这个礼布呢,因为是不透的啊。
跟我的面部要区分开。
不然的话它就走光了。
看一下它的不透明度啊。
不透明度是100,然后是冲淡颜色,它是白色的啊。
OK,然后呢,我们这个花朵呢。
把我们这个花朵也是应用上啊。
现在我已经有这个图案了。
所以可以,花朵也是用这个,有比较酒花形的这个效果的。
然后这个版片应该是用我们的这个,这里啊。
把这个名字改成一个,那个,蕾丝带。
好,那这个蕾丝带呢,我们其实也给它用一下这个面料。
肩带的一个面料。
直接肩带应用上去。
好,那这个位置它不对啊。
我们给它调整一下。
这里看不到,调到我们的纹理表面就可以看到了。
调整一下。
好,另一边也是。
把这边也调整一下。
这里的话我们把这个它的思维方向调整一下。
好。
这样的话就很快速的就把我们的这个。
面料的纹理给它应用上了啊。
那我们这边的话可以快速的,哎,我来到这个起色啊。
比如说增加一个起色。
嗯,在这里呢,我们可以快速的给它通过刚刚同相同的逻辑。
我们这边就不重复做了。
可以快速的去做到很多不同风格的这个印花。
那我们在这个第二个起色里面呢。
我们就打开这个,呃,纹理编辑器。
啊,你可以去再重新编辑调整。
每一个起色都是可以去重复的。
那这边的话我就不重复去,呃,进行这个操作了。
我们可以在编辑里面呢,因为我这边已经做过了啊。
所以我把这些都,元素都删除掉。
留一个底纹。
啊,我可以把这个拉进来。
哎,这是我完成的一个发挥。
那注意一下这个尺寸呢,和我的底部不,尺寸不匹配啊。
可以在下面看到它的尺寸。
我们可以把它贴上。
我们可以把它调到1024。
跟我的底部是相同的。
那我这样就可以看到它的一个尺寸了。
啊,应用并关闭。
啊,这样子的话我们这个花形就进来了。
啊,那在这边呢。
同样的。
啊。
你也可以再进行一个第三个。
更新。
那这边的话我这边不就不做了。
因为就是不停的重复这个工作啊。
然后这边的话我们来回到这个模拟状态。
哎,不是。
把这个三个那个棋色的窗口关掉。
那刚才的话我们是进行了一个印花的设计啊。
现在呢我们来到这个状态下看一下。
我们这个衣服的细节其实还不是特别的好。
啊,所以我们现在呢可以对我们这个服装进行一个品质的提升。
提升之前呢我们可以。
呃,因为等一下换动作会涉及到大量的模拟啊。
所以我们在。
提升品质之前呢比如说我想要。
啊。
猜。
在。
在material里面。
我想给它换一个动作。
那在这个时候去换。
先换动作再做那个。
品质提升。
啊,因为我们把粒子进去。
降低下来之后和模拟速度就会很慢了。
我们很多老用户应该都知道。
刚刚的话就是在花的那个纹理显示下透明的我看不到服装细节啊。
所以我现在切换到了这个。
呃,多颜色表面。
可以方便的去看到我各个版面之间的一个关系。
啊。
OK之后呢。
OK了。
那我接下来呢。
把这个给它动一下。
我接下来进行一个品质的提升。
那你可以选择一步去进行提升啊。
那我这边就直接选择一步提升吧。
呃,一步就是用这个提高服装品质工具啊。
510。
最后这个试穿不要勾。
它会速度很慢。
然后点击确认。
那这时候它一定会要花很多时间的。
它的速度会比较慢。
所以我们现在就给它慢慢的模拟一下。
静静的等待一会儿啊。
嗯。
好了。
好。
完毕。
好看到我们这条缝啊。
现在降低品质可以看到它不是很顺。
这时候我们可以把刚才就是我们加了那个。
嗯。
缝了这个荷叶边的这条线。
看一下啊。
你看这两条线啊。
我们去把它。
刚刚这条是根。
这条缝了。
Let's add a 100% elasticity to it
Because you may not be able to see this detail in a low quality state
Don't let it be stretched out, it's ugly
Let's put this in the front as well, 100% elasticity
At this point, you may need to spend some time on the model
Of course, you can also put the unrelated panels
For example, these ones, these ones, and these ones
All freeze them
Freeze them
Including this one
And also the back
You can also freeze the back
To make it faster
It's basically not moving anymore
It's almost done
And then
Pay attention to this
If you feel that this wrinkle is not very delicate and low-pitched
What can you do?
You can further reduce its particle density
It will remind you that you are very slow
Of course, you can just simulate the other parts of the frozen pillar separately
It will be faster
After reducing the particle density
The shape of its wrinkle will be more delicate
And then we just freeze it all
What does the frozen pillar do?
Let's take a look at the back
The back
Today's little trick
It's about the smark
If there is no bottom layer inside
This panel of the lining
It may be stretched through some fabrics
Because it itself
The silk fabric we use is very soft
Maybe you will eventually present one
The shape of the lower groove
That is, it will move
So I made a lining here
To support it inside
So that its entire shape will be more regular
In addition
About this panel
If we have a bottom layer
It has this
There is a bottom at the bottom
If you drag it
Its wrinkle will be more
Relative to no bottom drag
Will be more regular
More beautiful
So this is why
When I do it today
Will add a panel inside
I make it transparent now
In fact, it is not visible on the appearance
In the end
We see that this wrinkle is still very rough
We can reduce its particle density again
Take a look
Let's simulate it again
Now you can see
Its fold will be more and more delicate
I think three is almost the same
But if some people are particularly perfect
If you want to be more delicate
Just adjust the force to one
Of course, this is for the computer
This requirement will also be higher
We can take a look here
If you adjust it to one
Its speed will be very slow
But its effect will be very good
If you want to adjust it to one
It will be very smooth
Don't simulate the whole body
Just simulate this piece alone
It's still okay
Wait a minute
You can see these fold details
It will be better
Okay, the simulation is over
Now we come to this
Regular
In the form of surface texture
You can see this
The effect of this wrinkle
Then
Next, let's do
One of the effects of silk
It's very simple to make silk
First of all, we use the editor
To select my
This need to add
This line of silk
This edge line
Then select it
After that
You can see in the mouse editor
The length of the 2D line is 2075
Then
We will use the curved version tool
In a blank place
Create a long strip
The width
We can set it to 3 first
Set it to 3 mm
Then its length is 2075
Click to confirm
After the board is created
We will
Put this board
Give it to it
Just sew it to its corresponding edge
This is very simple
Single machine
After that
Let's give it
Add a silk fabric
Apply this fabric
On this board
Then
We will
Add this board
To our clothing
Note that
Its current version
Is too large
We can reduce it to 5
As this small board
Maybe it
If you want the details
Very good
May be reduced to 3
Or 1
But because it is very small
In fact, we can see
5 silk fabric is actually enough
We
After that
Come to the 2D window
Find this board
Then we right-click
Add it to the side
After adding
Need to check
Is the position of the addition correct
You can
Now we can see
Its position is actually wrong
Not right
Then we can
Take it out first
And then
Add it again
Add to
The side
Now we can see
It is right
After adding
Let's take a look
We can
Now we can
Simulate
Simulate first
Okay
Then
We can see
Its pattern
Is a bit wrong
We are now
Here
First
Use the editor
Pattern tool
First
Put my
This board
On it
Then
We can
First put my
This edge
To my
The edge of the sewing
Then
The other side
Give it
Press Shift
Push back
Push it
The width of this silk
Can be pushed a little more
Then
You can see it on the side
It is
There is
This feeling of opening
Then
This side is finished
Next
We come directly
Control D
The silk on the other side
Just copy it
OK
After copying
The other side is also
We need to add it to it
On the side
OK
Check it
The position is correct
But
The pattern
Is wrong
We
Move its pattern
Properly
Just
Okay
We
Added
The silk
In this way
Then
On the other side
Of course
You can also
Simulate
it
OK
Then
Next
In the same way
The addition of the other two sides
We can
OK
Then
Today
We
This style
It's done
Then
Finally
This place
The shoes
Is in our
This
Contact
Business program
Download
You can also go
Find a more suitable
Shoes
Not this
This
Blue
This pair of shoes
Finally
In fact
Look at my poster
On the poster
I just
Pulled one
Some flowers
I'll tell you about how to do it
This embroidery bag is actually very simple
Just
Two long strips
Plus a base
I sew it up
Then you sew two more
Two bags
This method is very simple
If you have finished
We have passed our basic class
And master class
Uh
Students
It should be
There is no problem at all
To make this bag
That's the key
This pattern
Maybe
You have to find one
Um
This kind of high-definition
Embroidery pattern
To scan
That's all
But about this flower
In fact
Before
Uh
In the master class
Mr. Yan
Have used
Uh
Use that
Bridge
To import some real
More realistic
This kind of model material
That class
Uh
You can
On that
Various
You can
On various websites
Or go to
Bridge
Or other websites
To find some of these
Uh
This kind of 3D resources
I also put this flower model
For him
Uh
Use a fixed needle
In this place
Adjust
Let this model's hand
Can look better
Is to hold this
Uh
The basket
That's it
Ah
And then finally
What about this rendering
It's actually very simple
Just made a
Uh
Simple background
Added a mirror
Ah
And then light
The final rendering
That's it for today
Our live class
That's it
Thank you for watching
Have a good weekend
Bye